TV를 볼 때에는 밝은 방에서 적당히 떨어져서 보도록 해!
While you're watching the television...
Selama menonton acara ini
...be sure to keep your distance and watch in a well-lit room!
pastikan berada di jarak yang cukup dan di ruangan yang terang!
Plan
Webdiver Production Committee
Original Plan
Ishikawa Hiroto
Dennou Boukenki
Series Composition
Chief Director
Sekijima Mayori
Okajima Kunitoshi
Character Design
Takahashi Naruyo
Concept Design
Color Scheme
Moriki Yasuhiro
Kawami Takuya
Production Designer
Director of Audiography
Composite Director
Iwase Eiji
Tanaka Hideyuki
Nagaushi Yutaka
Music
Music Producer
Music Collaboration
Hayashi Yuzo
Kumada Kazuo
Television Tokyo Music
Opening Theme
Lyrics
Composer/Arrangement
Oikawa Neko
Hirama Akihiko
Song
Columbia Japan
Production Collaboration
Animation Production
Animation Producer
AEON (We've)
Kachihide Yuki
Nomura Hiroshi
Producer
Iwata Makiko (TV Tokyo)
Yamazaki Tatsuji
Director
Negishi Hiroshi
Production
해방된 드라그온 사이트에 아이들은 없었어.
There were no children in Dragwon Site that we just freed.
Di Dragwon Site yang telah dipulihkan tidak ada anak-anak.
그 말은, 나머지는 다이탈리온 사이트에 있다는 거겠지.
That means the rest are in Ditalion Site.
Dengan begitu, yang tersisa tinggal Ditalion Site.
다이탈리온 사이트의 마스터 웹나이트 다이탈리온에 대한 데이터는 아무것도 없다.
There's no data regarding Ditalion, the Master Webknight of Ditalion Site.
Tidak ada data mengenai Ditalion, Master Webknight dari Ditalion Site.
다만, 전에 가륜에게서 들은 이야기는 있다.
But there's something I heard from Garyun.
Tapi, menurut informasi yang dikatakan Garyun waktu itu...
다이탈리온은 본디 시간의 신이라 불려 왔지만...
Ditalion calls himself as the god of time.
Ditalion menyebut dirinya sendiri sebagai dewa waktu.
시간의 신?
God of time?
Dewa waktu?
다이탈리온.
Ditalion.
자기 자신을 신이라고 부르다니, 대체 어떤 놈이길래?
To call himself a god makes me wonder what kind of guy he is.
Dia menyebut dirinya sendiri sebagai dewa? Orang macam apa dia itu?
그것보다도, 글라디온. 좋은 소식이야. 관리국에서 개발중이었던 매지컬 백신이 내일이면 완성된대!
Anyway, Gladion, good news. Magical Vaccine, which is being made in Administration Center,
Tapi, Gladion, ada berita bagus! Magical Vaccine yang sedang dibuat di World Link akan selesai besok!
will be completed tomorrow!
데리트로스를 격퇴할 백신이야. 이전에 데리트로스에게 부수어졌지만 그 때보다도 몇 배는 강해져 있다고 해.
It's the vaccine that will take Deletloss down. It once have been destroyed by Deletloss,
Itu vaksin yang bisa memukul mundur Deletloss. Memang sebelumnya Deletloss pernah merusaknya,
but now it is incomparably stronger than before.
tapi katanya vaksin yang sekarang sudah ditingkatkan kekuatannya!
매지컬 백신으로 다이탈리온 사이트의 아이들을 전부 구출할 수 있어뾰꼬!
With Magical Vaccine, we can rescue every children in Ditalion Site-pyoko!
Magical Vaccine bisa menyelamatkan anak-anak yang terperangkap-pyoko!
카이토!
Kaito!
형!
Brother!
Kakak!
카이토가 돌아올 거야. 카이토가.
Kaito will return. He definitely will.
Kaito pasti akan kembali. Pasti.
켄토.
Kento.
다이탈리온이 어떤 놈인지간에, 매지컬 백신이 있으면 무적이야!
Whoever the heck is Ditalion, as long as we have Magical Vaccine, we're invincible!
Biar seperti apapun Ditalion itu, asal ada Magical Vaccine kita tidak akan terklahkan!
안 그래, 글라디온?
Aren't we, Gladion?
Ya kan, Gladion?
그렇겠지.
I hope so.
Semoga saja.
시간의 지배자! 다이탈리온
Ruler of Time! Ditalion
Penguasa Waktu! Ditalion
[[=10.nref2]]
[[=10.nref2_1]]
[[=10.nref2_2]]
[[=13.nref3]]
[[=13.nref3_1]]
[[=13.nref3_2]]
[[=13.nref4]]
[[=13.nref4_1]]
[[=13.nref4_2]]
코스모 에이리어에서의 전투에서 승리한 켄토와 글라디온은
After winning on the battle in Cosmo Area,
Kento dan Gladion yang telalh memenangkan pertempuran di Cosmo Area
드라그온과 그 웹다이버, 아사바 나오키를 데리트로스의 속박에서 해방시켜 주었다.
Kento and Gladion freed Dragwon and his Webdiver, Asaba Naoki from Deletloss' restraint.
berhasil menyelamatkan Dragwon dan Webdiver-nya, Asaba Naoki dari cengkraman Deletloss.
매지컬 게이트의 존망이 걸린 전투가 점점 격렬해졌다.
The battle for Magical Gate became more and more fierce.
Pertempuran demi menyelamatkan Magical Gate semakin memanas.
최강의 마스터 웹나이트가 드디어 움직이기 시작했다.
Finally, the strongest Master Webknight has begun to move.
Penguasa site yang paling kuat akan mulai beraksi.
2시 50분 현재, 매지컬 백신 작업은 75% 달성되었습니다.
Now, 2:50, Magical Vaccine's activation progress is about 75% done.
Pada jam 2:50, proses pengaktifan Magical Vaccine sudah mencapai 75%
예정보다 느리군. 난 쿠라치를 도와주러 가겠다.
It's slower than the original plan. I'll go support Kurachi.
Sedikit lebih lambat dari rencana semula. Kalau begitu, aku akan membantu Kurachi.
-나머지는 잘 부탁한다.
-옙!
-I'll leave the rest to you.
-Got it!
-Tolong kalian lanjutkan, ya.
-Baik!
모두, 이제 한 걸음만 더 딛으면 된다. 모두 힘내 주길!
Just one more step. Everyone, do your best!
Semuanya, tinggal selangkah lagi. Berjuanglah!
주임님, 조금만 쉬는 편이...
Chief, how about taking a rest?
Profesor, lebih baik Anda istirahat.
괜찮아, 쿠라치야말로. 이 순간, 전혀 피곤하지 않은걸.
I'm okay. You yourself haven't gotten enough sleep lately too, have you?
Tidak apa-apa, kau sendiri belakangan ini juga hampir tidak pernah tidur, kan?
저도 괜찮습니다. 아우 쇼우를 생각하면 일분 일초라도 빨리 백신을 완성해야만 합니다.
I'll be fine. For my brother, Shou, I must finish the vaccine as soon as possible.
Tidak apa-apa. Kalau memikirkan adikku Shou, aku ingin menyelesaikan vaksin lebih cepat, biarpun cuma satu menit atau satu detik.
나도 마찬가지야. 내일은 카이토가 돌아오겠지. 그 때까지는 쉴 필요 따위 없어.
Same for me. When I think that tomorrow I can meet Kaito, I feel like I don't need to rest.
Sama denganku. Kalau memikirkan besok aku akan bertemu dengan Kaito, aku juga tidak perlu istirahat.
커피 가져다 드리겠습니다. 블랙으로.
I'll make you a coffee, then. A black one.
Akan kubuatkan kopi, ya. Yang kental.
고마워.
Thanks.
Terima kasih, ya.
고장
Out of order
Dalam perbaikan
미안, 늦었어! 아니, 눈을 떴는데 시계가 고장나 있지 뭐야.
Sorry for being late! I woke up just to find my alarm clock broken.
Maaf, ya, aku terlambat! Habis, jamnya sedang rusak.
-어.
-역시.
-Ah.
-I was right!
-Wah?
-Ternyata benar!
어, 왜?
Um, what's the matter?
Ah, kenapa?
사실은 우리도 이제야 도착했어.
Actually, we just arrived here too.
Sebenarnya kami juga baru datang.
그럼 켄토도.
So it's happening in Kento's place, too.
Jadi di rumah Kento juga, ya.
뭔 이야기야?
What are you talking about?
Kalian bicara apa?
고장
Out of order
Dalam perbaikan
시계 말야, 시계. 나도 아오이도 일어나 보니까 집 시계가 고장나 있더라고.
We're talking about clocks. Both in Aoi's and my home, when we woke up this morning, the clock on the entire home had already broken.
Mengenai jam. Di rumahku dan juga di rumah Aoi, saat bangun tadi pagi, jam di seluruh rumah sudah rusak.
고장
Out of order
Dalam perbaikan
지금은 매지컬 게이트에 이상은 없어뾰꼬.
There's no abnormalities in Magical Gate at the moment-pyoko.
Saat ini belum ada keanehan di Magical Gate-pyoko.
혹시 모르니 웹나이트들에게 각 에이리어를 순찰하게 할게뾰꼬.
Just in case, I'll tell the Webknights to patrol in their areas-pyoko.
Untuk jaga-jaga, kuperintahkan Webknight untuk berpatroli di area masing-masing-pyoko.
믿고 맡길게.
Please do.
Tolong, ya.
-우리는 관리국에 가자.
-그래.
-Let's go to the administration center.
-Sure.
-Kita ke Stasiun World Link.
-Iya.
그리피온, 샤크온, 피닉스온, 출발뾰꼬!
Griffion, Sharkon, Phoenixon, launch-pyoko!
Griffion, Sharkon, Phoenixon, meluncurlah-pyoko!
여기저기에서 시계가 부서지는 일이 일어났다는 소리는 들었어.
Yeah, I've heard that clocks all over the place has broken.
Iya, aku sudah dengar kalau dimana-mana terjadi peristiwa jam rusak.
그래도 지금 여기 관리국에서는 이상은 없어.
But there was no sign of abnormality at the administration center until now.
Tapi, sampai saat ini, belum terjadi masalah di Stasiun Pengendali ini.
다행이다!
What a relief!
Syukurlah!
이미 매지컬 백신 프로그램은 90% 이상 만들어졌어.
Magical Vaccine program is already completed by more than 90%.
Sekarang, program Magical Vaccine sudah terselesaikan lebih dari 90%
예정대로 진행된다면 타임 에이리어에 백신 주입은
If it goes according to the plan, the vaccine's injection into Time Area can--
Kalau berjalan sesuai rencana, pemasukan vaksin ke Time Area bisa--
실, 실례, 레나 씨.
Sorry, Ms. Rena.
Aduh, maaf, ya, Rena.
괜찮아요. 피곤해 보이시네요.
It's all right. You must be tired as well.
Tak apa. Anda pasti juga lelah, ya?
뭐, 단지 철야 작업을 며칠째 하다 보니... 죄송합니다.
Well, you could say that. I've been working all night lately, so...
Ya, begitulah. Habis, terus-terusan begadang, jadi...
뭐, 그럼 얼마 안 남으셨을 테니 힘내세요.
Anyway, we're almost there. Let's do our best.
Tinggal selangkah lagi, kan? Mari, kita berjuang.
자, 아리스가와 박사님이 계신 곳은 개발실. 갈까?
Well then, we need to bring these files to Prof. Arisugawa's development room. Let's go.
Nah, sekarang kita harus membawa ini ke ruang penelitian Profesor Arisugawa. Ayo, semuanya.
여긴 그리피온. 스카이 에이리어, 현재 이상 없음.
This is Griffion. Nothing weird in Sky Area for now.
Ini Griffion. Sampai sekarang tidak ada keanehan di Sky Area.
알겠어뾰꼬! 그대로 쭉 패트롤을 계속해뾰꼬.
Got it-pyoko! Continue with your patrol-pyoko.
Baik-pyoko! Lanjutkan berpatroli-pyoko.
아니?
What's that?
Hei!
뭐, 뭐야?
What the?!
Apa itu?!
그리피온!
Griffion!
뭐, 뭐야?
The heck?
Kenapa bisa begini?
유우키 군, 이건...?
Yuuki, what's going on?
Taketo, ada apa ini?
잘 모르겠습니다! 이건 현상은...
I don't know! I've never seen such thing...
Aku tidak tahu! Fenomena apa lagi ini...
아야...
Ouch...
Aduh...
뭐, 뭐야, 방금 그거!
What was that just now?!
Tadi itu, apa yang terjadi?!
왠지 공기가 안 무거워졌어.
The air became heavy somehow.
Suasananya jadi terasa berat.
컴퓨터실!
The computer room!
Ruang komputer!
뭐, 뭐야, 이 아이들은.
Who are these children?
Darimana mereka ini?
직원 전부 어디 갔지?
Where did the staff go?
Kemana perginya para staf?
미안, 쿠라치.
Apologies, Kurachi.
Maaf, ya, Kurachi.
-설마!
-이 아이들은!
-No way!
-So the kids here are...!
-Jangan-jangan!
-Semua anak yang ada di sini itu adalah...!
샤크온!
Sharkon!
주임님!
Chief!
Profesor!
-아빠!
-할아버지!
-Dad!
-Grandpa!
-Ayah!
-Kakek!
-주임님!
-Chief!
-Profesor!
-아빠!
-Dad!
-Ayah!
-할아버지!
-Grandpa!
-Kakek!
아오이! 기계 가지고 왔어?
Aoi! Did you bring my clothes?
Aoi! Kamu bawa baju ganti untukku, kan?
뭐야, 켄토도 왔구나?
Oh, Kento's here too!
Wah, Kento juga ikut, ya!
주임님.
Chief....
Profesor...
레, 레나 누나!
Re- Rena!
K-Kak Rena!
어째서 이런... 관리국의 어른들이 전부 아이들이 되어버렸잖아!
How did this happen... all the adults in the center became children!
Apa yang terjadi... orang dewasa di Stasiun Pengendali, semua berubah menjadi anak kecil!
끔이야! 악몽일 거야, 시간이 되돌아갔다니!
It's a dream! I must be having a bad dream! It's impossible for time to go back!
Ini mimpi! Aku sedang bermimpi buruk! Masa waktu bisa berjalan mundur!
시간?
Time?
Waktu?
-시간의 신!
-어?
-God of time!
-Huh?
-Dewa waktu!
-Hah?
이게 다이탈리온의 능력인가 봐!
This might be Ditalion's ability!
Mungkin ini adalah perbuatan Ditalion!
다이탈리온?
Ditalion?
여긴 피닉스온. 현재 미확인 물체에 공격을
Phoenixon here. I am being attacked by an unidentified object-
Di sini Phoenixon. Sekarang aku sedang diserang oleh benda tidak dikenal-
피닉스온!
Phoenixon!
-이얍!
-아직이다!
-Take that!
-I'm not done yet!
-Rasain lu!
-Awas kamu, ya!
이런...
Err...
Haduh...
-이야압!
-질까보냐!
-Get lost!
-Like I'm losing!
-Terima ini!
-Masih belum!
오지 마!
You're playing dirty!
Kamu curang!
아빠!
Dad!
Ayah!
아빠! 백신 완성은 했어?
Dad! Are you done with the vaccine?
Ayah! Vaksinnya sudah selesai, belum?
아직!
Not yet!
Belum!
아빠!
Dad!
Ayah!
시끄럽긴. 이 게임 끝나고 완성할 거야!
You're being naggy! We'll do it after the game!
Uuh, berisik! Nanti kuselesaikan, kok, setelah main game!
아, 하고말고! 이얏!
Huh, you're pretty good! Watch out!
Aah, boleh juga kamu! Awas!
할아버지도 참! 계속 나한테 공부해 공부해 하실 때는 언제고!
Come on, Grandpa! Just when you're the one who keeps telling me to study!
Huh, Kakek! Padahal kan biasanya terus-terusan menyuruhku belajar!
엉망이네.
What a disaster.
Yang benar saja.
아, 카론이 불렀다!
Ah, Karon called me!
Ah, ini Karon!
켄토. 큰일이야뾰꼬. 그리피온도 샤크온도 피닉스온도 당해버렸어뾰꼬.
Kento, we're in trouble-pyoko. None of Griffion, Sharkon, and Phoenixon survived-pyoko.
Kento, gawat. Griffion, Sharkon dan Phoenixon sudah dikalahkan-pyoko.
뭐라고?!
What?!
Apa katamu?!
켄토, 당장 와 줘뾰꼬!
Kento, come here quickly-pyoko!
Kento, cepat datang ke sini-pyoko!
알았어!
Alright!
Baiklah!
매지컬 게이트에 플러그 잇!
To Magical Gate, Plug It!
Menuju Magical Gate, Plug It!
웹다이브! 글라디온!
Webdive! Gladion!
긴급 발진 대기중.
Emergency dispatch, standby.
Siap untuk diluncurkan.
글라디온, 출동.
Gladion, shoot.
다이탈리온은 우리가 아는 것 하나 없는 미지의 적이다. 켄토, 충분한 주의가 필요해.
Ditalion is an enemy we don't know anything about. Kento, be careful.
Ditalion adalah lawan yang sama sekali belum kita ketahui. Berhati-hatilah, Kento.
미지의 적...
An unknown enemy..
Lawan yang belum diketahui, ya...
켄토, 코스모 에이리어에 미확인 물체가 있어뾰꼬!
Kento! There's an unidentified object in Cosmo Area-pyoko!
Kento! Di Cosmo Area ada sesuatu yang tidak dikenal-pyoko!
알겠어!
Got it!
Baiklah!
Brought to you by Subdiver
저 놈이구나!
That damned thing!
Kurang ajar!
뭐야?!
What just happened?!
Apa yang terjadi?!
어딜 달아나!
You're not running away!
Tidak akan kubiarkan kabur!
여, 여긴?
Where are we?
Di, dimana ini?
타임 에이리어야, 켄토!
We're at Time Area, Kento!
Kita di Time Area, Kento!
타임 에이리어?
Time Area?
이 녀석! 몸을 보여라!
Damn you! You've finally shown up, huh!
Keterlaluan! Jadi kau itu di situ, ya!
웹체인지! 글라디온, 파이터 모드!
Webchange! Gladion, Fighter Mode!
저렇게 작은 녀석이 신이라는 다이탈리온인가.
Is that little robot the one who calls himself as god?
Webknight sekecil itu jadi penguasa waktu?
어이, 좀 기다려!
Hey, stop right there!
Hei, berhenti kalian!
부탁이니까 제발 좀 돌아와.
I beg you, please continue your work.
Kumohon, lanjutkanlah pekerjaan kalian.
간식 줘! 간식!
Give us some snack! Snack time!
Minta permen, dong! Permen!
시끄러워! 간식은 일 끝나고!
Shut up! Work first, snack later!
Enak saja kau! Permennya nanti setelah bekerja dulu!
울고 싶은 건 나야.
I'm the one who should be crying.
Yang mestinya nangis itu aku.
아싸! 이겼다! 이겼어!
Yay! I won! I won!
Hore! Aku menang!
-젠장!
-아싸!
-Damn!
-Yay!
-Sial!
-Aku hebat!
자, 약속대로! 게임 끝났으니까 빨리 백신을 만들어야지?
Now, keep your promise! Now that the game's done, finish the vaccine, please?
Kalian, kan, sudah janji. Game-nya sudah selesai. Sekarang coba selesaikan vaksinnya, ya?
-아오이! 한 번만 더!
-나도!
-Aoi, one more game!
-Great idea!
-Aoi, boleh sekali lagi?
-Iya!
다시 한번 승부다!
One more match!
Satu pertandingan lagi!
안 돼!
No!
Tidak boleh!
할아버지도 아저씨도 말한 대로 해야지! 노는 건 그 다음에.
Enough, both of you! This is not the time for you to play around!
Kakek, Paman, sadarilah! Ini bukan saatnya untuk bermain!
매지컬 게이트에는 아직 많은 아이들이 갇혀 있는데!
There are still a lot of children trapped in Magical Gate!
Saat ini, masih banyak anak-anak yang terperangkap di Magical Gate!
백신이 있으면 매지컬 게이트를 해방할 수 있어! 데리트로스를 쓰러뜨리고!
With the vaccine, we can free Magical Gate and take Deletloss down!
Asalkan ada vaksin, kita bisa merebut kembali Magical Gate, dan bisa mengalahkan Deletloss!
무기 선택: 그란발칸.
Weapon Selection: Granvulcan.
Pilihan Senjata: Granvulcan.
뭐야?!
What the?!
Apa?!
사라졌어?
It disappeared?
Hilang?
빨라!
It's fast!
Cepat sekali!
내 한계 속도를 훨씬 뛰어넘었어!
He is faster than my maximum speed!
Kecepatannya jauh melebihi kecepatan maksimalku!
제군! 우리 사명은 데리트로스에게서 매지컬 게이트를 되찾고 갇힌 아이들을 구출하는 것이다!
My friends! Our mission is to take Magical Gate back from Deletloss and save the trapped children!
Para staf sekalian! Tugas kita adalah untuk merebut kembali Magical Gate dari Deletloss dan menyelamatkan anak-anak yang terperangkap!
데리트로스.
Deletloss.
제군! 모두 힘을 합해 매지컬 백신을 완성하자! 노는 건 그 다음에!
Everyone! Let's complete the Magical Vaccine together! After then we'll play!
Semua! Ayo kita bekerja sama menyelesaikan Magical Vaccine! Main-mainnya setelah itu saja!
응.
Yeah.
Baiklah.
일어났어, 쿠라치?
You've finally woken up, Kurachi.
Kau sudah sadar, ya, Kurachi?
잘 때 아니야.
It's not the time to sleep.
Ini bukan saatnya untuk tidur.
한시라도 빨리 백신을 완성해야 해!
We must complete the vaccine as soon as possible!
Kita harus menyelesaikan vaksinnya secepat mungkin!
아, 넵!
G-Got it!
B-Baik!
이 빛은 뭐지?
What's with this light?
Cahaya apa ini?
켄토! 글라디온!
Kento! Gladion!
켄토!
Kento!
백신은 아직이야? 글라디온이 위험해!
Is the vaccine ready yet? Gladion's in danger!
Vaksinnya masih belum juga, ya?! Gladion dalam bahaya!
할아버지!
Grandpa!
Kakek!
좋아, 준비 OK!
Alright! Preparation OK!
Bagus! Persiapan selesai!
여긴 항상 준비되어 있습니다!
We're always ready to launch the vaccine!
Kami di sini siap meluncurkan vaksin kapan saja!
쇼우 누나, 매지컬 백신은요?
Rena, how's Magical Vaccine?
Kak Rena, bagaimana Magical Vaccine-nya?
프로그램 입력 95%.
Program input 95%.
Input program sudah 95%.
96...
97...
98...
99...
100%!
매지컬 백신 완성!
Magical Vaccine is ready!
Magical Vaccine sudah selesai!
서둘러! 매지컬 백신 장전!
Hurry up! Inject Magical Vaccine!
Cepat! Injeksi Magical Vaccine!
-장전!
-Inject!
-Injeksi!
목표, 타임 에이리어!
Target, Time Area!
목표, 타임 에이리어! 조준은 OK에요!
Target, Time Area! It's now aimed properly!
Target, Time Area! Siap diluncurkan!
발사 5초 전!
5 seconds until shoot!
Peluncuran 5 detik lagi!
4...
3...
2...
1...
발사!
Shoot!
Luncurkan!
백신, 매지컬 게이트에 진입! 타임 에이리어에 향하고 있습니다!
The vaccine has entered Magical Gate! It's heading for Time Area!
Vaksin sudah memasuki Magical Gate! Sekarang menuju ke Time Area!
그래! 가라!
Good! Now go!
Bagus! Ayo maju!
저, 저건?
That's...
Itu, kan...
매지컬 백신이 완성됐어뾰꼬!
Magical Vaccine is finished-pyoko!
Magical Vaccine sudah selesai-pyoko!
박사님! 성공이에요!
Professor, it worked!
Profesor, vaksinnya bekerja!
응!
Yeah!
Ya!
해냈구나!
We did it!
Berhasil!
매지컬 백신 덕분에 살았구나!
We're saved by Magical Vaccine!
Berkat Magical Vaccine, kita bisa tertolong!
녀석이 멈췄어! 켄토!
He stopped to move! Kento!
Saat ini Ditalion sedang lengah! Ayo, Kento!
좋아! 그란블레이드!
Alright! Granblade!
Ayo! Granblade!
지금이야! 켄토!
Kento, now!
Sekarang, Kento!
브레이크 슛!
Break Shoot!
Right at the target!
Tepat di sasaran!
아싸!
Yay!
Berhasil!
어?
Huh?
Apa?
할아버지!
Grandpa!
Kakek!
아오이!
Aoi!
-주임님!
-레나!
-Chief!
-Rena!
-Profesor!
-다행이군요!
-어휴, 이게 대체 무슨...
-What a relief!
-Geez, that was sure one hell of problem.
-Syukurlah!
-Ya ampun, tadi itu benar-benar gawat, ya.
이, 이건!
What the?!
I-Ini?!
부활했어?!
It revived?!
Dia pulih kembali!
이건!
This is!
Ini!
엄청 크다...
I-it's huge...
Be-besar sekali...
나는 다이탈리온. 나는 시간의 신.
I am Ditalion. I am the god of time.
Aku adalah Ditalion. Aku adalah dewa waktu.
저게 진짜로...
That's the real...
Jadi ini Ditalion...
다이탈리온.
Ditalion.
yang sebenarnya.
Screenplay
Araki Ken'ichi
Storyboarding
Yamamoto Yuusuke
Staging
Okajima Kunitoshi
Voice Actor
Yuuki Kento
Gladion
Arisugawa Aoi
Asaba Naoki
Takeuchi Junko
Kobayashi Yumiko
Sugita Tomokazu
Kikuchi Shiho
Karon
Kaida Yuki
Voice Actor
Yuuki Kaito
Takagi Reiko
Yuuki Taketo
Ookura Masaaki
Arisugawa Professor
Tobita Nobuo
Kurachi Rena
Kakazu Yumi
Voice Actor
Sharkon
Yoshino Hiroyuki
Griffion
Nakamura Yuuichi
Phoenixon
Suzumura Ken'ichi
Garyun
Konishi Katsuyuki
Ending Theme
Lyrics
Oikawa Neko
Composer
Suzuki Kisaburo
Arranger
Kouno Yougo
Singer
Kageyama Hironobu
Columbia Japan
Production Cooperation
Animation Production
AEON (We've)
Subtitle
Subdiver
ファン字幕
サブダイバー
Production
Thank you for watching!
다음 이야기 미리보기
Preview for Next Episode
Episode Selanjutnya
동면하는 전사, 와이버리온.
The hibernating warrior, Wyverion.
Prajurit yang sedang tertidur, Wyverion.
와이버리온이 있다면 글라디온은 최강의 빅토리 모드가 돼!
With Wyverion, Gladion can use his most powerful mode, Victory Mode!
Asalkan ada Wyverion, Gladion bisa menggunakan mode terkuatnya, Victory Mode!
다이탈리온을 쓰러뜨리고 매지컬 게이트를 되찾고 싶으니까
To defeat Ditalion and take Magical Gate back...
Untuk mengalahkan Ditalion dan mengambil kembali Magical Gate...
네 힘을 빌려 줘!
Please, lend us your power!
Pinjamkanlah kami kekuatanmu!
우리 함께 싸우자, 와이버리온!
Let's fight together, Wyverion!
Mari kita bertarung bersama, Wyverion!
전뇌모험기 웹다이버의 다음 이야기!
Next episode of Dennou Boukenki Webdiver!
Di episode Dennou Boukenki Webdiver selanjutnya!
Thanks for watching! - Subdiver
See you at http://subdiver.soreepeong.com/ !